Fred Ho Papers
© 2005 University of Connecticut
- Series XXI: Early Asian American Literature, 1981-1992
  - Notes, undated (Box 2:, Folder E)
  - Tanka, undated (Box 2:, Folder F)
  - Chinese American: Songs From Gold Mountain, undated (Box 2:, Folder G)
  - Articles, undated (Box 2:, Folder H)
  - Articles, 1984 (Box 2:, Folder I)
  - Articles, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder J)
  - Articles, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder K)
  - Articles, 1992 (Box 2:, Folder L)
  - Articles, 1992 (Box 2:, Folder M)
  - Articles, 1991 (Box 2:, Folder N)
  - Articles, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder O.)
  - Essay: Chinese American History, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder P)
  - Sui Sin Far Edith Eaton: The First Chinese American Fiction Writer, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder Q)
- Series XXII: Asian American Poetry, Literature, 1974-1985
  - Poetry: Fred Ho, undated (Box 2:, Folder A)
  - Poetry: Fred Ho, 1975 (Box 2:, Folder B)
  - Poetry: Janice Mirikitani, undated (Box 2:, Folder C)
  - Poetry: Genny Lim, 1975 (Box 2:, Folder D)
  - Poetry: Lydia Lowe, undated (Box 2:, Folder E)
  - Poetry: Cathy Song, undated (Box 2:, Folder F)
  - Poetry: Todd Lee, 1980 (Box 2:, Folder G)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder H)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder I)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder J)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder K)
  - Poetry, 1984 (Box 2:, Folder L)
  - Poetry, 1976 (Box 2:, Folder M)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder N)
  - Poetry, 1976 (Box 2:, Folder O)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder P)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder Q)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder R)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder S)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder T)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder U)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder V)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder W)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder X)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder Y)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder Z)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 2:, Folder AA)
  - Poetry, 1980 (Box 2:, Folder AB)
  - Correspondence, undated (Box 2:, Folder AC)
  - Notes, undated (Box 2:, Folder AD)
  - “By the Shadow of the Orange Grove”: Russell C. Leong: Script, 1985 (Box 2:, Folder AE)
  - Literature: Essays, undated (Box 2:, Folder AF)
  - Literature: Essays, undated (Box 2:, Folder AG)
  - Literature: Frank Chin, undated (Box 2:, Folder AH)
  - Poetry: Article, undated (Box 2:, Folder AI)
  - Literature, undated (Box 2:, Folder AJ)
  - Literature, 1974 (Box 2:, Folder AK)
  - Literature: Book Review: Toshio Mori, 1979 (Box 2:, Folder AL)
  - Literature: Promotional Material: Taro Yashima, 1981 (Box 2:, Folder AM)
  - Literature: Promotional Material: Shawn Wong, undated (Box 2:, Folder AN)
  - Publishers, 1983-1984 (Box 2:, Folder AO)
  - Film: Essays, undated (Box 2:, Folder AP)
  - War Brides: Essay, 1984 (Box 2:, Folder AQ)
  - Art, undated (Box 2:, Folder AR)
  - Asian American Artistic Expression, undated (Box 2:, Folder AS)
  - Art: Chinese Celebration, 1976 (Box 2:, Folder AT)
  - Book Review: Kim, undated (Box 2:, Folder AU)
  - Poetry, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder AV)
- Series XXIII: Review of Asian American Literature, 1982
  - Literature: Book Review: Kim, Elaine. Asian American Literature (Original in display case in AASI) (Box 2:, Folder A)
  - Literature: Notes for review of Kim, Asian American Literature(Original in display case in AASI) (Box 2:, Folder B)
- Series XXIV: Fred Houn Poetry, 1974
  - Poetry (Box 2:, Folder A)
  - Poetry (Box 2:, Folder B)
  - Poetry (Box 2:, Folder C)
  - Poetry (Box 2:, Folder D)
  - Poetry (Box 2:, Folder E)
  - Poetry (Box 2:, Folder F)
  - Poetry (Box 2:, Folder G)
  - Poetry (Box 2:, Folder H)
  - Poetry (Box 2:, Folder I)
  - Poetry (Box 2:, Folder J)
  - Essay: “Toward an Asian American Culture,” (Original in display case in AASI) (Box 2:, Folder K)
- Series XXV: Fred Ho Poetry, 1974-1983
  - Untitled, undated (Box 2:, Folder A)
  - Untitled, 1975 (Box 2:, Folder B)
  - New Dawn (Comin' in Bright and Strong), 1975 (Box 2:, Folder C)
  - Untitled, 1975 (Box 2:, Folder D)
  - letter for Gwen (and good-bye Yale), 1975 (Box 2:, Folder E)
  - I say your name, 1975 (Box 2:, Folder F)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 2:, Folder G)
  - Change for Chinks, undated (Box 2:, Folder H)
  - Christmas letter, 1976 (Box 2:, Folder I)
  - Poem for Azania, undated (Box 2:, Folder J)
  - A dialogue: Tomorrow is Now!, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder K)
  - Liberation Haiku, 1983 (Box 2:, Folder L)
  - Tanka, undated (Box 2:, Folder M)
  - Tanka: Male Chauvanism, undated (Box 2:, Folder N)
  - Haiku: Sisters, undated (Box 2:, Folder O)
  - Chi Lai! (Song for Gold Mountain Warriors), 1983 (Box 2:, Folder P)
  - A night haiku, undated (Box 2:, Folder Q)
  - Haikus: Love/Struggle in 5 parts, undated (Box 2:, Folder R)
  - violence and DEATH, 1974 (Box 2:, Folder S)
  - Japanese syllyabic verse: Tanka, undated (Box 2:, Folder T)
  - Syllyabic verses: Haiku, 1975 (Box 2:, Folder U)
  - Haiku #3 (6:25 pm), 1974 (Box 2:, Folder V)
  - Third World Understanding, 1975 (Box 2:, Folder W)
  - Original syllyabic verses, undated (Box 2:, Folder X)
  - Untitled, undated (Box 2:, Folder Y)
  - To you, for every peaceful moment, 1975 (Box 2:, Folder Z)
  - Praise Trilogy for the People's Republic of China, 1975 (Box 3:, Folder AA)
  - I say your name, undated (Box 3:, Folder AB)
  - Poem for Azania (Black Homeland), undated (Box 3:, Folder AC)
  - Big Tenor Man (Poem for Archie Shepp), undated (Box 3:, Folder AD)
  - Colored Opportunists I Have Known, undated (Box 3:, Folder AE)
  - The autobiography of a chink, 1979 (Box 3:, Folder AF)
  - Ode to the third world, undated (Box 3:, Folder AG)
  - Dare to Struggle, Dare to Win!, 1979 (Box 3:, Folder AH)
  - Untitled, 1979 (Box 3:, Folder AI)
  - Krushcovism - Trotskyism - Gang of Four Thought, 1979 (Box 3:, Folder AJ)
  - Wanted for the Murder of Little Lincoln Louie: The United States of America, undated (Box 3:, Folder AK)
  - We'll Make Tomorrow (Kayo's Song), 1983 (Box 3:, Folder AL)
- Series XXVI: Reviews and Essays, undated
  - Poetry: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - Poetry: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder B)
  - Poetry: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder C)
  - Music: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder D)
  - Music: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder E)
  - Music: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder F)
  - Literature: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder G)
  - Literature: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder H)
  - Theatre: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder I)
  - Theatre: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder J)
  - Theatre: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder K)
  - Art: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder L)
  - Art: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder M)
  - Art: Reviews and Essays (Box 3:, Folder N)
- Series XXVII: Genny Lim, 1983-1987
  - “The Sky Never Stops”: Script, 1983 (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - “XX”: Script, 1986 (Box 3:, Folder B)
  - “La China Poblana”: Script, undated (Box 3:, Folder C)
  - Correspondence, 1987 (Box 3:, Folder D)
  - Correspondence, 1983 (Box 3:, Folder E)
  - “Ganbaro!” by Fred Houn: Score, 1983 (Box 3:, Folder F)
- Series XXVIII: Asia Society, 1976-1987
  - Articles: Hong Kong, 1987 (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - Articles: Asia in American Textbooks, 1976 (Box 3:, Folder B)
- Series XXIX: Louis Chu, undated, 1984
  - Louis Chu, 1984 (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - Literature: Review of Eat a Bowl of Tea, undated (Box 3:, Folder B)
  - Notes, undated (Box 3:, Folder C)
- Series XXX: Pilippino American Literature, undated, 1985
  - History: Chronology, undated (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - History: Essays, undated (Box 3:, Folder B)
  - History: Essays, undated (Box 3:, Folder C)
  - History: Essays, undated (Box 3:, Folder D)
  - Maps: Philippines, undated (Box 3:, Folder E)
  - “Bamboo That Snaps Back”: Proposal, 1985 (Box 3:, Folder F)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder G)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder H)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder I)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder J)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder K)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder L)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder M)
- Series XXXI: Royal F. Morales, 1974-1981
  - Makibaka: The Pilipino Struggle
    - Text, 1974 (Box 3:, Folder A)
    - Articles, 1981 (Box 3:, Folder B)
- Series XXXII: Filipinos in America, undated, 1972-1976
  - The Filipinos in America: A Chronology and Fact Book, 1976 (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - Articles, undated (Box 3:, Folder B)
  - History: Chronology, undated (Box 3:, Folder C)
  - Discrimination: Essays, undated (Box 3:, Folder D)
  - Hawaii: Essays, undated (Box 3:, Folder E)
  - Sambayanan: Mission Statement, undated (Box 3:, Folder F)
  - Literature: Book Orders, undated (Box 3:, Folder G)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder H)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder I)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder J)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder K)
  - Poetry, 1972 (Box 3:, Folder L)
  - Poetry, undated (Box 3:, Folder M)
- Series XXXIII: H.T. Tsiange, 1935-1938
  - “China Marches On,”, 1938 (Box 3)
  - “The Hanging on Union Square,”, 1935 (Box 3)
- Series XXXIV: FUSANG and Chinese Mythology, undated
  - Essays, undated (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - Notes, undated (Box 3:, Folder B)
- Series XXXV: Early Chinese American Literature, 1983
  - Xiao Lin Li, 1983 (Box 3)
- Series XXXVI: Japanese American Tanka, 1987-1988
  - Notes, undated (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - Tomoe Tana: Essays, 1988 (Box 3:, Folder B)
  - Tomoe Tana: Correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 3:, Folder C)
  - Tomoe Tana: Articles, 1987 (Box 3:, Folder D)
  - Tomoe Tana: Tanka, undated (Box 3:, Folder E)
  - Poetry, 1987 (Box 3:, Folder F)
- Series XXXVII: Janice Mirikitani, 1983
  - Janice Mirikitani, 1983 (Box 3)
- Series XXXVIII: Asian American Theatre, 1979-1995
  - Synopsis: Warrior Sisters, 1995 (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - Synopsis: Journey Beyond the West, 1990-1991 (Box 3:, Folder B)
  - Photographs, 1980-1981 (Box 3:, Folder C)
  - Life in the Fast Lane, 1984 (Box 3:, Folder D)
  - Articles, 1981 (Box 3:, Folder E)
  - Articles and Notes, 1979-1982 (Box 3:, Folder F)
  - Performance Programs, undated (Box 3:, Folder G)
  - Performance Programs: Yellow Fever, 1982 (Box 3:, Folder H)
  - Script: “A Chinaman's Chance,” by Fred Ho, 1989 (Box 3:, Folder I)
  - Japanese Traditional Dances, undated (Box 3:, Folder J)
  - Performance Programs: La Mama, 1998 (Box 3:, Folder K)
  - Once Upon a Time in a Chinese America..Martial Arts, 1999 (Box 3:, Folder L)
- Series XXXIX: And the Soul Shall Dance, 1975-1979
  - Articles and Reviews, 1975-1979 (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - Script, 1979 (Box 3:, Folder B)
- Series XL: Monkey King Ballet, 1987-1990
  - Articles and Posters, 1990 (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - Performance Programs, undated (Box 3:, Folder B)
  - Photographs, 1987 (Box 3:, Folder C)
- Series XLI: Chinaman's Chance Press, 1987-1989 (Box 3)
  - Information, 1987-1989
- Series XLII: Fred Ho Scores, undated, 1976-1983
  - “Warrior or Sister” Sheet Music & Notes (Box 3A:, Folder A)
  - “Dare to Struggle, Dare to Win!”, undated (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - “Blues to the Freedom Fighters”, 1976 (Box 3:, Folder B)
  - “GANBARO! A Tribute to the Japanese American Struggles”, 1983 (Box 3:, Folder C)
  - “Survivors / For My Father”, undated (Box 3:, Folder D)
  - “Bound Feet”, undated (Box 3:, Folder E)
  - “Profits Enslave the World”, undated (Box 3:, Folder F)
  - “Uproar in Heaven” from “Journey Beyond the West: The New Adventures of the Monkey King (Where no white man has gone before!)”, undated (Box 3:, Folder G)
  - “Happiness in the Peach Garden” excerpt from “The Monkey Suite”, undated (Box 3:, Folder H)
  - Act 3: “Monkey Meets the Spider Spirit Vampires”, undated (Box 3:, Folder I)
  - “Turning the Cheek Only Gets You Two Sore Cheeks!”, undated (Box 3:, Folder J)
  - “Contradiction, Please! The Revenge of Charlie Chan”, undated (Box 3:, Folder K)
    (items G-K originals are on display in the AASI)
- Series XLIII: Fred Ho Biographical Information, undated, 1996
  - Career Summaries, undated (Box 3:, Folder A)
  - Papers Written About Fred Ho (Box 3:, Folder B)
    - Fred Ho and the Development of an Afro-Asian American Music, undated
  - Shock the Monkey - Art and Activism of Fred Ho, 1996 (Box 3:, Folder C)
- Series XLIV: Career Summaries, undated
  - Amiri Baraka (Le Roi Jones), undated (Box 3:, Folder D)
  - Sin-yan Shen, undated (Box 3:, Folder E)
  - Esther Iverem, undated (Box 3:, Folder F)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 3:, Folder G)
- Series XLV: Books, Videos, Recordings, 1982-1997
  - Albums
    - Fred Houn and the Asian American Art Ensemble, “Bamboo That Snaps Back,”, 1985. (Box 4A)
    - Fred Houn, featuring the Asian American Art Ensemble and Kulintang Arts, “A Song for Manong,”, 1988.
    - Fred Houn and the Afro-Asian Music Ensemble, “Tomorrow is Now!”, 1985.
    - Fred Houn and the Afro-Asian Music Ensemble, “We Refuse To Be Used and Abused,”, 1988.
    - Wineke, F. “Rage On.”, 1984
  - Books (Box 4B)
    - Ho, Fred; Wei-Han and Ron Sakolsky, eds. Sounding Off! Music as Subversion Resistance / Revolution. Brooklyn, NY: Autonomedia and Contributors, 1995.
    - Ho, Fred and Ruth Margraff. Night Vision a first and third world vampire opera. Brooklyn, NY. Big Media Records, 2000.
  - Videos
    - Fred Ho's Afro-Asian Ballet, “Monkey Meets the Spider Spirits” and “White Wash”
    - “A Chinaman's Chance: A New American Opera,” by Fred Ho, Brooklyn Academy of Music, April 9, 1989
    - “A Chinaman's Chance,” Promo Concert Version, November 1987, San Francisco
    - Art Ensemble Performance, November 20, 1982 at Studio 2
    - World of Jazz, August 1986, Wesleyan University
    - Shajiabang: Spark Amid the Reeds. Part I Scene 1-7. Directed by Dr. E. Wichmann (R. Kevin's Cast) Copyright 1994
    - City Arts: Monkey at Guggenheim
    - Rodgers and Hammerstein's “Flower Drum Song.”
    - Fred Ho, “Community Reception.”, August 19, 199
    - Fred Ho, “Phillip Bither Interview.”, August 28, 1999
    - Fred, Ho, “Art and the Revolution Struggle.”, August 24, 1999
    - Fred, Ho, “Minnesota Public TV.”, August 25, 1999
  - CDs
    - Vijay Iver, “Memorophilia,”, 1995.
    - Dean Laabs and Jeff Song, “Invisible Maniac,”, 1994.
    - Jeff Song and Matt Turner, “Love & Fear,”, 1992.
    - virtual fleality, “red flea,”, 1996.
    - Jeff Song and Lowbrow, “Rules of Engagement,”, 1996.
    - Coltrane, John. “Dear Lord, Mew-Levino Duo,”, 1999.
    - Broken Speak, “I was born with two tounges,”, 1999.
    - Balaz, Joe, “Electric Laulau,”, 1998.
  - Cassettes
    - Long 2, “People of Color,” and “Here and Now,”, 1990.
    - Vijay Iver, architextures,”, 1996.
    - Interview with Fred Ho, WBAI Radio, January 28, 1997
    - Fists of Fury.
    - Kihakuno Vibrations.
    - Making Contact; cash and culture., October 15, 1999.
    - WNYE FM Prime Time with P.J. Show Seven Version 1.
    - Jon Jang, Fred Ho
    - Afro American Music Ensemble., July 31, 1982
  - Promotional materials, 1975-1977 (Box 5)
  - Names of Records Artists (Box 6)
    - “Eight Warriors” of special collection of Artist Yusuyan Yusuyan Bluofusan
    - “Sacrifice Xuzhou City”
    - “Twice in Jail”
    - Special Collection of Artist Yusuyan Including:
    - “Assemble to Pick Tassels”
    - “Conquer City Fan”
    - “The Fate of the Fishmen”
    - “The White Arch”/“General Yangzongbao” Style of Ye
    - “Red Plum House”
    - “Three Mothers' Teaching Sons” Mr. Mei Lan Fang
    - “The Adventure of Spring and Autumn” Style of Huang
    - “The Adventure of Fancy House”
    - “Angle the Golden Tortoise” Style of Lee
    - “Lady XI SI”/“Wenzao Pass” Mr. Mei Lan Fang
    - “The Magic Lotus Lamp”
    - “An Emerald Hairclasp”
    - “The Biograph of Hong Fu”
    - “The Grave for a Couple”
    - “The Drunken Concubine” Mr. Mei Lan Fang
    - “Clap Hands for the Third Time” Mr. Cheng Xian Qiu
    - “The Third Lady in Your Family” Style of Xun
    - “Losing the Fort” Yu Su Yan
    - “Yuchang Sword
    - “Empty City”
    - “Monument to Lee
    - “Story of Black Pot”
    - “Famen Temple”
    - “Yellow Crane Pavillian”
    - “To Conquer City of Yeng Yang”
    - “Go to the Heaven”
    - “Searching in the Mountain”
    - “The Adventure of Spring -N- Autumn” Style of Zhang
    - “A Precious Pearl” Guan Xaohua
      (from “The Fate of the Fishmen”)
    - “Red Scar” Tan Cheng Er
    - “Red Scar” Tan Cheng Er
    - “New “Yu Tang Chun” Style of Zhang
    - “New “Yu Tang Chun” Style of Zhang
    - “New “Yu Tang Chun” Style of Zhang
    - “The Hill Wujia” Style of Ma
    - “Generals from Family Yang” Yang Baoseng
    - “Generals from Family Yang” Yang Baoseng
    - “Black Dragon House”
    - “Suwu's Tending Sheep”
    - “Judge Bao sentence Lu Qi Lang to Death”
    - “Mountain Ding Jiang” Style of Yuan
    - “The Hill Wujia” Style of Ma
    - “Lady XISI” Mr. Mei Lan Fang
    - “Village Muke”
    - “Meet in Coincidence”
    - “Dragon Plays with Phoenix”
    - “Releasing Chao” Yu Su Yan
    - “Selling Horse and giving Performance of Sword Play”
    - “The Fourth Son Visiting his Mother”
    - “Making an Exchange at Place of Executation”
    - “Three Candidates for Higher Education” Style of Lee
    - “The Story of General Yu and his Mother”
    - “Put Five Dragons into Cages” Style of Lee
    - “In the Stockaded Village”
    - “Hatred of Butcher Zao”
    - “Stealing a Horse”
    - “Tears of Remote Mountain” Mr. Cheng Xian Qiu
    - “Ten Orders” Styles of Ma & Dan
    - “Ten Orders” Styles of Ma & Dan
    - “Cry in Front of Ancestral Grave” Style of Sun
    - “Murder Against Tang” Styles of Chen & Lei & Xiao
    - “Murder Against Tang” Styles of Chen & Lei & Xiao
    - “Murder Against Tang” Styles of Chen & Lei & Xiao
    - “Wenzao Pass” (II)
    - “DaBao Kingdom”
    - “Hong Yang Cave”
    - “A Deep Night”
    - “Empty City” (II)
    - “Butting Against a Stele”
    - “Scolding Officer Chao”
    - Piano Concerto (Yellow River) Conductor: Lee De Lun
      - Announcements, Flyers, Brochures, 1998-1999 (Box 7)
      - Nation of Islam, 1975
      - Speech—“Mao, the Black Panthers and the Third World Strike”, 1999
      - Afro Asian Music Ensemble, undated
        - Press Articles, undated
      - Black Panther Ballet Suite, 1998
      - Announcements, Flyers and Brochures, 1998
      - Announcements, Flyers and Brochures, 1997
      - Yakota, Ryan, 1994
      - People's Conference against Imperialist Globalization, 1997
      - Warrior Sisters (Score), undated
      - Happiness in the Peace Garden (Score), undated
      - Monkeys Origin (Score), undated
      - “Asian American Composers: Jason Hwang and Fred Ho”, 1997
      - Announcements, Flyers and Brochures, 1997
      - Chinese American Intercollegiate Conference, 1998
      - “Revolutionary Monkey Business”, 1991
      - “Finding Affinity: Asian American Women...”, undated
      - Speech, undated
      - Asian American Left Forum, undated
      - Korea Society, 1998
      - Correspondence, 1997-1999
      - Photographs, 1997
      - Ho, Fred Prize, 1999
  - CDs
    - China Exchange
    - Warrior Sisters
    - Fred Ho and the Monkey Orchestra
    - Fred Ho and the Afro Asian Ensemble
    - Monkey: Part One
    - Fred Ho and the Afro Asian Music Ensemble (Turn Pain Into Power)
  - VHS
    - Fred Ho on Kai's Odyssey, 1999
    - Oversize
    - Poster
    - Sheroes 1999 Calendar
- Periodicals
  - Gidra
    - v.1:no.1-v.1:no.5, (1969:April-1969:August) (Box 8)
    - v.1:no.7-v.1:no.9, (1969:Oct.-1969:Dec.)
    - v.2:no.1-v.2:no.10, (1970:Jan.-1970:Nov.)
    - v.3:no.1-v.3:no.6, (1971:Jan.-1971:July)
    - v.3:no.9-v.3:no.11, (1971:Sept.-1971:Nov.) (Box 9)
    - v.4:no.3, (1972:Mar.)
    - v.4:no.5-v.4:no.6, (1972:May-1972:June)
    - v.4:no.9-v.4:no.10, (1972:Sept.-1972:Oct.)
    - v.5:no.1-[v.5:no.4], (1973:Jan.-1973:April)
    - v.5:no.6-v.5:no.12, (1973:June-1973:Dec.)
    - v.6:no.1-v.6:no.2, (1974:Jan.-1974:Feb.)
    - v.6:no.4, (1974:April)
    - v.20 n.?, 1990
    - v.1n.1, Spring 1999
  - Unity
    - v.1:no.1-v.2:no.16, (1978:Sept.-1979:Aug.) (Box 10)
    - v.2:no.19-v.2:no.24, (1979:Sept.-1979:Dec.)
    - v.3:no.2-v.3:no.9, (1980:Jan.-1980:May) (Box 11)
    - v.3:no.11-v.3:no.23, (1980:May/June-1980:Dec.)
    - v.4:no.1-v.4:no.8, (1981:Jan-1981:April/May)
    - v.4:no.8-v.4:no.19, (1981:May-1981:Dec.) (Box 12)
    - v.5:no.1-v.5:no.19, (1982:Jan.-1982:Dec.)
    - v.6:no.1-v.6:no.12, (1983:Jan.-1983:Aug./Sept.) (Box 13)
    - v.6:no.14-v.6:no.17, (1983:Sept./Oct.-1983:Nov.)
    - v.6:no.19, (1983:Dec./1984:Jan.)
    - v.7:no.1-v.7:no.10, (1984:Jan.-1984:June/July)
    - v.7:no.12-v.7:no.13, (1984:Aug./Sept.-1984:Sept./Oct.)
    - Asian Week v.20:no.11, (1998:Nov.) (Box 14)
    - Forward motion supplement 1, (1955)
    - Getting together v.4:no.5-v.4:no.6, ((1973:Mar.-1973:Mar.)
    - Nikkei, (1980:Aug.)
    - LTPRO news v.1:no.1, (1977:Aug.)
    - 1 misc. issue in Chinese
    - 1 misc. pamphlet, untitled
    - Lavoz de Berkeley v.9n.1, Spring 1999
    - Hardboiled v.2n., 4 April 1999
    - Bridge (Box 15)
      - v.1:no.3, (1971:Nov./Dec.)
      - v.1:no.6, (1972:July/Aug.)
      - v.2:no.1-v.2:no.3, (1972:Sept./Oct.-1973:Feb.)
      - v.7:no.3, (!980:Spr./Sum.)
      - v.8:no.2, (1982/1983:Wint.)
      - v.9:no.2, (1984)
    - Bamboo Girl
      - v.1 - v.4, v. 5 (undated)
    - A. magazine, 1997:Feb.-Mar. 1998:Feb.-Mar.; (2 c.) (Box 16)
    - AABANY memo v.8:no.1, (1998:May)
    - Arts spectrum 25th anniversary issue, 1973-1998
    - Asian Pacific American Heritage Festival [program], 16th-17th 1996-1997
    - Asian Pacific American Institute for Congressional Studies [newsletter]1998:Spring
    - Chinese Progressive Association 10th Anniversary Celebration [program], 2.c.
    - Crosscurrents v.20:no.2, (1997:Fall/Wint.)
    - Downbeat, 1998:Mar.
    - Earshot jazz v.14:no.10, (1998:Oct.)
    - East Coast Asian American Scholars Conference proceedings, 1986:Oct.
    - East Coast Asian Student Union 20th Anniversary Conference [program], 1998:Feb.
    - East wind 1989 v.7:no.1, (1989:Spr./Sum.); 2.c
    - I.W.K. journal no.1-no.3, (1974:Aug.-1976:Jan.)
    - Jericho movement, 1998:Nov.
    - NAPALC review v.4:no.1, (1998:Spr.)
    - Newsweek v.80:no.24, (1997:Dec.); 2.c.
    - Rice, 1988:Oct.
    - San Francisco examiner magazine, 1998:Oct.
    - Shades of power v.1:no.1, (1998:Spr.)
    - Sounding board, 1998:June
    - Unity monthly, 1980:Jan., 1980:Nov.-1981:Jan., 1981:June
    - Unity monthly “ Chinese side”, 5 issues
    - World is yours no. 4, (1996:Dec.)
    - Metamorphosis v.1n.1, Spring 1999
    - The Onyx, March 1999
    - Rethinking Schools v.13 n. 3, Spring 1999
    - Asian Outlook v.11 n.1, November 1999
    - Pacificties v.22 n.2, Winter 1999
    - Legacy to Liberty; Manuscript (Box 17)
- Additions
  - “Once Upon A Time” Photographs, 1999 (Box 18)
  - “Once Upon A Time” Drafts, Scripts, Press Releases, 1999-2003
  - “Once Upon A Time” Responses from high-schoolers, 2003
  - “Once Upon A Time” Costume Maintenance, 2001
  - “Once Upon A Time” Seattle, 2001
  - “Once Upon A Time” Boston, 2001
  - “Once Upon A Time” Guggenheim, 2000
  - “Once Upon A Time” New Jersey, 1999
  - “Once Upon A Time” Playbills & Ads, 2003; (5 folders)
  - “Warrior Sisters” Calling Script, 2000
  - “Warrior Sisters” Props, Costumes, Press, 2000
  - “Warrior Sisters” @ the Kitchen, 2000
  - “Black Panther Suite” Development, 1995-1999
  - “Black Panther Suite” Budget, 1998-1999
  - “Black Panther Suite” Publicity, 1999
  - “Black Panther Suite” Research w/ photos, 1966-1999; (3 folders)
  - National Question, 1992, 1991-1993
  - Papers by Others, 1999-2003
  - Mumia Abu-Jamal Material, 1999-2002
  - Susan Rosenberg Material, 1999-2001
  - Chicago ABC Zine Artwork of Todd Hyung-Rae Tarselli, 2002
  - Chicago ABC Zine, 2002
  - Somebody blew up America, by Amiri Barker, 2001
  - It's About Time, 2000-2003
  - For A Better World, 2001-2002
  - Correspondence, Personal w/ photos, 1998-2002; (2 folders) (Box 19)
  - Correspondence, Professional, 1989-2002
  - Correspondence & Drawings of Todd (Hyung-Rae) Tarselli, 1999-2002
  - Kerness, Bonnie, Articles on Prison system, 1997-2000